我十二岁的时候得到了我的第一个猫（调制解调器），一个1200波特ACE兼容款。
I was 12 years old when I got my first modem, a 1200 baud ACE compatible. I
我开始上网，不是上因特网，而是局域网BBS。
started getting online, not the internet online, local
与此同时，雅皮士们（中上阶层年轻专业人士）正在
BBSs. At around the same time, yuppie was supporting
支持第一个砖头大的移动手机，因为最早的GSM网络
the first brick-sized mobile phones as the first
开始发布了。快进不到17年来到2007，
GSM network started rolling out. Fast forward less than
iPhone面世，跟着一年不到
17 years to 2007, and the iPhone launches, followed
Android也来了。几乎是一夜之间，
less than a year by Android. And almost overnight,
我们开始期待从我们的手中获取
we've come to expect the world's information in the
世界上的信息。只是安卓问世后的六年
palm of our hands. Just six years after the first
时间，他正在驱动从手机到
Android phone launched, it's powering everything from phones to
平板，手表，电视和汽车每一件东西。所以我们
tablets, watches, TVs and cars. So where do we go
接下去会去向何方？最显而易见的是使得
next? The most obvious answer is enabling the same
手持设备云能够链接近五十亿人。
handheld cloud connecting computing platform to the next 5 billion
随着硬件变得越来越便宜而强大，更多的
people. As hardware becomes cheaper and more powerful, more of
世界人口会有能力获得互联网接入的电脑。
the world's population will be able to get internet-connected computers.
智能手机将会驱使这一切成为可能。
And the smartphone is going to be what makes
为了让一切更便捷，我们正在探求
it possible. To facilitate this, we're seeing new approaches
上网的新途径，网格网，白色空间，或者甚至
to getting online, mesh networks, white spaces, or even
是Google的Loon项目。我们很快就会见到全世界范围普遍存在的
Google's Project Loon. We'll hopefully soon see ubiquitous world-wide internet
网络连接变成现实。同时，智能手机
connectivity become a reality. At the same time, smartphones
将会开始消失。正如一旦计算机变成我们
will start to disappear. In the same way that
洗盘机，汽车或者电视的一部分时
we don't think of computers as computers once they
我们就不再把他们当作计算机了，当手机
become part of our dishwashers, cars, or TVs, we'll stop
消失到我们的手表和其他未知事物中去，我们也会不再把他们当作手机。
thinking of mobiles as such when they disappear into our
我们会开始期待
watches and [UNKNOWN]. We'll come to expect that anything that
能够通过无线因特网连接能改善的东西
can be improved through the incorporation of a wireless internet
都会有那么一个。为了使这发生，我们需要
connection will simply have one. For that to happen, we need
找到相比用鼠标，键盘和触摸屏，
to find more creative ways to interact with computers than
更有创造性的与计算机交互的方式。
using mouse, keyboards and touch screens. I can all ready pick
我已经可以拿起我的时候或者举起我的手腕，来找到Google，
up my phone or lift my wrist, address Google, and
做搜索，发送消息或邮件，设置定时，或者记录笔记而不需要
perform searches, send texts or email, set alarms, or take notes
触摸屏幕或者键盘。
without having to touch a screen or keyboard. Screen
屏幕正在变得过于锐利，
themselves have become so   that pixel densities aren't
像素密度已非人眼可感知的。
perceptible to the human eye. And the team at
Google X的团队正在研发可以测量血糖含量的隐形眼镜。
Google X are building contact lenses capable of measuring blood
通俗点讲，我们只是
sugar levels. Speaking of senses, not only can I
通过把手机面朝上面朝下那种来控制我们的手机，
control my phone by putting it either face up or
他有一组传感器如同军舰一般。
face down, it has a battery of sensors similar
光线感应，温度改变，气压计，
to an [UNKNOWN] class warship. Light meters, temperature changes, barometers,
陀螺仪，这些都可以用来替代
gyroscopes, all of which can be used to
文字输入或者自动处理。可穿戴设备，汽车，
replace text entry or automate processes. Wearables, cars,
以及温度调节器为传感器引入了更多的可能性。
and thermostats introduce even more possibilities of sensors.
把这一切都接入云端，
Connect all of that to the cloud, and the
可能性是无穷无尽的。Android的未来
possibilities are endless. Future of Android isn't a
不是一台更强大的手机处理系统。
more powerful phone operating system. It is the
这会是不可见的，无处不在的，云计算背后的大脑。
brains behind invisible, ubiquitous, cloud connected computing. So
所以我们今天用来学习构建酷炫应用的技能
the skills we learn today to build cool apps
也会是我们将来
are the same skills we'll use tomorrow
控制周遭一切时所使用的。我们已经
to control everything around us. We've taken
向未来迈出了第一步。我已经迫不及待看到你们接下去会做的了。
the first step into that future. I can't wait to see what you do next.